<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WTPersonal</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WTPersonal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wtpersonal.xyz/&#34;&gt;T. Wu&lt;/a&gt; Powered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wangchucheng/hugo-eureka/&#34;&gt;the Eureka&lt;/a&gt; theme for &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 05:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Collection</title>
      <link>/posts/memo/collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 05:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/memo/collection/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memo</title>
      <link>/posts/memo/memo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 17:07:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/memo/memo/</guid>
      <description>&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash; Introduction Background Now, the network infrastructure has spread out from submarine communications cable system to low earth orbit communications system. It breaks through space constrains. Wherever people live, Everyone can share their own feelings, knowledge and experience on the internet. Therefore, The place where people can acquire knowledge is transferred from library to the internet. That further leads to a massive increase in depth and breadth of knowledge that people have acquired. On the internet, we can find a lot of blogs, articles and notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang</title>
      <link>/posts/memo/golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 17:07:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/memo/golang/</guid>
      <description>Programming Format text string in console display (X)  Looking for the solution. The &amp;lsquo;\t&amp;rsquo; did not work, especially, cannot align upper and lower text Consider to try &amp;lsquo;imgui&amp;rsquo;  Network </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox Commands</title>
      <link>/posts/proxmox/command/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 17:01:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/proxmox/command/</guid>
      <description>Record usd Proxmox VE commands. 目录 import disk img Import disk img Transfer .img disc image file to Virtual Machine(vm) disk. The example is to transfer openWRT image file to VM disk. qm importdisk [VM id] [image path] [storage id] Example: qm importdisk 100 ./openwrt.img local-lvm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unix-like System Commands</title>
      <link>/posts/command/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 23:00:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/command/</guid>
      <description>Record infrequently used but potential useful commands
Contents  iperf3 - Network speed test  iperf3 Test network speed between devices. First, open server-side iperf/iperf3 service, then, test it by client-side iperf/iperf3 application. Under windows system, the application is iperf3.exe.
Open server-side iperf3 service iperf3 -s -p 5201  Open client-side iperf3 service iperf3 -c [ip address] -p 5201  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox changes Sources</title>
      <link>/posts/proxmox/sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 16:52:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/proxmox/sources/</guid>
      <description>The official Proxmox provides a enterprise source, but we do not need to subscription a enterprise license in home use. We only need the free and well-supported community source. By the way, we get a limitation download speed from international connect (1Mbps approximately) in home use, even I bought 300Mbps download speed plan. Thus, need to change system software sources as well. It will need Ali Yun source andUSTC source</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
